<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">FitnessBuddy2Go</string>
    <string name="createmyworkout_button">Create My Workout</string>
    <string name="exercise_library_button">View Exercise Library</string>
    <string name="guide_button">Info</string>
    <string name="workout_generator_title">Workout Generator</string>
    <string name="exercise_library_title">Exercise Library</string>
    <string name="info_title">How to Use the App</string>
    <string name="title_exercise_list">Exercises</string>
    <string name="title_exercise_detail">Description</string>
    <string name="age">Enter Age</string>
    <string name="weight">Enter Weight(lbs)</string>
    <string name="height">Enter Height(in)</string>
    <string name="selfassess">Enter self assessment of physical condition (from 1–10)</string>
    <string name="Generate">Generate</string>
    <string name="GoToExerciseLibrary">Go To Exercise Library</string>
    <string name="info_text1">Welcome to FitnessBuddy2Go, your mobile personal workout creator and exercise reference. This is a highly convenient and versatile tool, since most of the exercises in this app do not require any equipment.</string>
	<string name="info_text2">To create your workout in Workout Generator, enter your info in their respective 
	fields and click generate.
	For the self assessment field, you must rate your overall physical condition 
	on a scale of one (least fit) to ten (most fit). You can also access the exercise library from this screen which contains all the exercises found within the app. 
	</string>
	<string name="info_text3">A good estimate of your overall fitness
	would be the amount of regular push-ups and sit-ups you can do without stopping, as well as the time it takes you to run 1.5 miles or 2.4 km. If you are a male: rating of (1-2) - less than 15 push-ups and 30 sit-ups and run completed in greater than 16:00, rating of (3-4) - 
	15-25 push-ups and 30-49 sit-ups and run completed in 14:01-16:00, rating of (5-6) - 26-35 push-ups and 50-70 sit-ups and run completed in 12:01-14:00, rating of (7-8) - 36-49 push-ups and 71-89 sit-ups and run completed in 10:46-12:00, rating of (9-10) - 50 push-ups and 90 sit-ups or more and run completed in less than 10:46.  If you are a female: 
	rating of (1-2) - less than 5 push-ups and 31 sit-ups and run completed in greater than 19:00, rating of (3-4) - 
	5-9 push-ups and 31-40 sit-ups and run completed in 18:31-19:00, rating of (5-6) - 10-20 push-ups and 41-55 sit-ups and run completed in 15:55-18:30, rating of (7-8) - 21-35 push-ups and 56-79 sit-ups and run completed in 13:31-15:54, rating of (9-10) - 36 push-ups and 80 sit-ups or more and run completed in less than 13:31. If your score for 
	sit-ups, push-ups and the mile and a half run are different, then take the average of the three and round it to the nearest whole number.\n\n
	If you find any exercise too difficult to perform in your generated workout, then you can perform any of the exercises that come before it in the same category, and slowly make your way to the recommended exercise as your fitness improves.
	</string>
	<string name="Disclaimer"><b>Use this app and any workouts generated by this app at your own risk. 
	If you have any serious medical conditions, do not attempt any of the exercises without seeing a physician or doctor. 
	Do not attempt the exercises any further if you experience pain or aching in any part of your body. The information contained within this app is not meant as a substitute for professional medical advice and care. The developer of FitnessBuddy2Go will not be held responsible for any injuries that may arise from the use of this app.</b></string>
	<string name="Credits"><u><b>Image Credits</b>\n\n</u>Background and exercise images (excluding self taken photos) courtesy of bigstockphoto.com;\nPush-Up image 1: Courtesy of Pearson Scott Foresman/Used under CC BY 3.0;\nSuperman image: Courtesy of Kennguru/ Used under CC BY 3.0;\nChin-Up images: Courtesy of Everkinetic/ Used under CC BY 3.0;</string>
	<string name="Developer"><b>Developed by Chaitanya Varier</b></string>
	<string name="developer_site"><b>Developer webpage: </b><i>fitnessbuddy2go.com</i>\n\n</string>
	
	
</resources>
